Finding Aid for the Jonathan Friedlander Collection of Middle Eastern Americana LSC.1314
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books, 1908 - 2003; 9 boxes (4.5 linear feet)
  - Romance novels, 1931 - 2006; 1 box (.5 linear feet)
    - Desert of desire San Diego, CA: Corinth., 1966; 159 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Back cover reads: "During the incredible Algerian troubled times, pitched battles were breaking out all over the city, turning each wanton oasis into a...Desert of Desire." Leisure Book number LB1171.
    - Desert virgin New York, NY: Harlequin, March., 2006; 187 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Creator: Marton, Sandra
      Back cover reads: "Cameron Knight is a fearless troubleshooter on a mission in the desert kingdom of Baslaam... Leanna DeMarco is a ballerina; she's been abducted to dance for the sultan of Baslaam..." Uncut series, number 2525.
    - Exposed: the Sheikh's mistress New York, NY: Harlequin, September., 2005; 187 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 6)
      Creator: Kendrick, Sharon
    - I married a sheikh New York, NY: Silhouette Books, August., 2001; 248 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Creator: De Vita, Sharon
      Back cover reads: "In the aftermath of Joe Colton's explosive birthday bash, honorary son Sheik Ali El-Etra had his own fires to extinguish." The Coltons series.
    - In the Sheikh's marriage bed New York, NY: Harlequin, March., 2005; 187 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Creator: Morgan, Sarah, 1948-
    - Love-slave to the Sheikh New York, NY: Harlequin, August., 2006; 186 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Creator: Lee, Miranda
      Back cover reads: "Sheikh Bandar bin Saeed al Serkel had lived life in the fast lane. But now this oil-rich billionaire was facing a roadblock: he had a brain tumor." Uncut series, number 2556.
    - Panther and the pyramid New York, NY: Leisure Books, September., 2006; 337 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Creator: Vanak, Bonnie
      Back cover reads: "Graham Tristan has been tormented too long. He is physically strong: during his childhood exile, he rode with the Khamsin - Egyptian Warriors of the Wind."
    - Perfumes of Arabia New York, NY: Harlequin, February., 1986; 186 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Creator: Wood, Sarah
      Back cover reads: "An English girl in an Arabian dream...Normally Jeannie hated men like Tarik–masterful, dynamic, ruthless. But the desert country of Riyam began weaving its timeless magic on her." Harlequin Romance number 2814.
    - Sheikh New York: Dell., 1921; 240 pages, 16 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 12)
      Back cover reads: "Diana Mayo, a strikingly beautiful English girl, was left in infancy to the sole care of her brother, Sir Aubrey, upon the tragic deaths of their parents." Dell number 174.
    - Sheikh and the virgin secretary Toronto: Silhouette, December., 2005; 248 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 13)
      Creator: Mallery, Susan
      Back cover reads: "The wedding of my dreams was only days away...until I discovered my fiance had a nasty habit of unfaithfulness. So to mend my wounded pride, I turned to the most eligible man I knew: my boss, Prince Rafiq of Lucia-Serrat!" Special Edition series, Desert Rogues subseries, number 1723.
    - Sheikh's captive bride New York, NY: Harlequin, August., 2005; 186 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 14)
      Creator: Stephens, Susan
    - Sheikh's castaway New York, NY: Silhouette Books, November., 2004; 184 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Sheikh's disobedient bride New York, NY: Harlequin, June., 2006; 188 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Creator: Porter, Jane, 1964-
      Back cover reads: "Sheikh Tair lives by the rules of the desert. When he finds Tally has broken a sacred law, endangering the safety of his tribe, Tair has to act. Tally is kept like a harem girl, but every time she tries to escape, the hostile desert drives her back." Number 2542.
    - Sheikh's innocent bride New York, NY: Harlequin, January., 2006; 187 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 17)
      Creator: Graham, Lynne
      Back cover reads: "Desert prince Shahir has three simple rules: never sleep with a virgin, never get involved with an employee and never get married....But rules are made to be broken!" Number 2511.
    - Sheikh's proposal New York, NY: Harlequin, January., 2003; 184 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 18)
      Creator: McMahon, Barbara
      Back cover reads: "Sara Kinsale is stunned to be thrown together with a prince of the desert, and even more so to find herself unbelievably attracted to the elusive Sheikh Kahrun bak Samin." High Society Brides series, number 3734.
    - Sheikh's virgin New York, NY: Harlequin, June., 2005; 185 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Starlight over Tunis New York, NY: Jove Books, February., 1987; 177 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 20)
      Creator: Cartland, Barbara
      Back cover reads: "An Adventurer was planning an expedition to recover an ancient Roman treasure - at the expense of the wealthy, handsome Marquis of Quinbourne, who was cynical but amused." New Camfield Novel of Love number 50.
    - Stolen by the Sheikh New York, NY: Harlequin, February., 2006; 186 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 21)
      Creator: Morey, Trish
      Back cover reads: "Sheikh Khaled Al-Ateeq has asked Sapphire Clemenger to design the wedding gown of his intended bride. But there's more to Khaled's deal than meets the eye: Sapphy must accompany him to his desert palace, and she's forbidden to meet the bride-to- be. How strange when she's told the bridal gown's measurements are her own... Sapphy realizes that she's been stolen by the sheikh - because she's his chosen wife!" Number 2522.
    - Tangier nights New York: Jove Publications., 1981; 187 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 22)
      Creator: Ross, Clarissa
      Back cover reads: "Life becomes a shadowy maze in which her closest friends may be her foes...and two men vie for her passion..HASSAN..and the dark-eyed, daring Arab sheik, who makes her a slave to his love..."
    - Undercover sultan New York, NY: Silhouette Books, August., 2001; 188 pages, 17 centimeters (Box 21, Folder 23)
      Back cover reads: "Sheikh Haroun al Muntazir was honor-bound to recover a priceless family jewel... but what was the lovely operative Mariel de Vouvray's mission?" Desire series, Sons of the desert: The sultans subseries, number 1385.
  - Pocket-sized books, 1930 - 1968; 1 box (.5 linear feet)
    This subseries consists of small adventure fiction books. Cover illustrations within this subseries include Orientalist imagery.
    - Beasts of Tarzan Chicago, IL: Publishers Syndicate., ca. 1930; 426 pages, 11 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Creator: Burroughs, Edgar Rice
      Part of Big Little Books series. Cover features illustration of Tarzan keeping a tiger by a leash.
    - Dan Dunn secret operative 48 Chicago, IL: Publishers Syndicate., 1934; 318 pages, 11 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 2)
      From cover: "Crime never pays." Part of Big Little Book series. Cover features an illustration of a detective catching a Chinese man.
    - Hanna-Barbera's Shazzan: the glass princess Racine, WI: Western., 1968; 248 pages, 13 centimeters, 2 copies (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Creator: Christensen, Don
      Excerpt from page 10: "For the twins, Chuck and Nancy Barrot, this timeless land of the Arabian Nights was still a place of wonders–even though they had already seen so much."
    - Jack Hubert in the camels are coming Akron, OH: The Saalfield Publishing Company., 1935; unpaged, 14 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 4)
      From cover: "A Gaumont-British production." Cover features illustration of man saluting in the desert with a camel caravan in the background.
    - Jerry Parker police reporter and the Candid Camera Club Racine, WI: The Whitman Publishing Company., 1941; 293 pages, 12 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Creator: Wallen, Jack
      Cover is an illustration of a pharoah's tomb.
    - Mickey Mouse and the magic lamp Racine, WI: Whitman Publishing Company., ca. 1930; 428 pages, 11 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Creator: Disney, Walt
      Part of Better Little Books series. Cover features an illustration of a genie emerging from a lamp being held by Mickey Mouse.
    - Phantom and desert justice Racine, WI: The Whitman Publishing Company, 1941., 1939; 424 pages, 12 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Creator: Moore, Ray
      Excerpt from page 9: "Four hundred years ago, a man was washed up on a remote Bengal shore. He had seen his father killed and his ship scuttled by Singh pirates."
    - Phantom and desert justice Racine, WI: The Whitman Publishing Company, 1941., 1939; 424 pages, 12 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Creator: Falk, Lee
    - Tarzan Racine, WI: Whitman Publishing Company., 1967; 254 pages, 13 centimeters, 2 copies (Box 22, Folder 8)
      From cover: "The mark of the red hyena." Part of Big Little Books series. Cover features illustration of Tarzan and woman being chased by a man wearing a keffiyeh.
    - Tom Mix and his circus on the Barbary Coast Racine, WI: Whitman Publishing Company., 1940; 430 pages, 11 centimeters (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Part of Better Little Books series. Cover features illustration of man wearing a cowboy hat punching a man wearing a keffiyeh.
- Serials, 1917 - 2004; 7 boxes, 1 oversize box (3.5 linear feet)
  This series consists of serial publications ranging from pulp fiction, comic books, men's adventure magazines, and magazines. The illustrations and photography featured in these materials visibly document American Orientalism in popular culture, including erotic Orientalism and stereotypical representations of Middle Eastern people, history, and places.
  - Pulp fiction, 1917 - 1953; 5 boxes (2.5 linear feet)
    This subseries includes Orientalist adventure and mystery stories in serial form.
    - Adventure Kokomo, IN: Popular Publications, Vol. 124, no. 2., 1941 January; 112 pages, 22 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 1)
      From cover: "Sahara squadron."
    - Adventure Chicago, IL: Popular Publications, Vol. 109, no. 6., 1943 October; 161 pages, 24 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 2)
      From cover: "Zero hour." Cover painting by Maurice Bower.
    - Adventure Chicago, IL: Popular Publications, Vol. 120, no.2., 1948 December; 126 pages, 24 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 3)
      From cover: "The noose of Allah."
    - Amazing stories Lake Geneva, WI.: TSR, Incorporated, Vol. 22, no. 7., 1948 July; 162 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Creator: Courcy, Dorothy de
      From cover: "The man from Agharti."
    - Amazing stories Lake Geneva, WI.: TSR, Incorporated, Vol. 22, no. 7., 1948 July; 162 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Creator: Courcy, John de
    - Amazing stories Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Incorporated, Vol. 22, no. 5., 1948 May; 178 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Creator: Browning, Craig
      From cover: "Armageddon." Excerpt: "This is a stage through which all worlds go; when its inhabitants face "the battle of Armageddon." Illustrated by Robert Gibson Jones.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 237, no. 6., 1933 April 22; 144 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Creator: Mason, F. V. W.
      From cover: "The snaring of Sgt. Frost." Excerpt: "A firing squad promises a pleasanter death than the fate of a Legion spy caught in Touareg territory." Cover design by Paul Stahr.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 244, no. 4., 1934 February 3; 144 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Creator: Newsom, J. D.
      From cover: "Lion of Morocco." Excerpt: "While he lasted, Abdullah ben Inghazi, the self-styled Lion of the Tafilalet, came so near to causing a major conflagration in South Morocco that the French authorities have not yet recovered from the shock." Cover painting by Harry H. Hohnhorst.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 244, no. 2., 1934 January 20; 144 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Creator: Carse, Robert
      From cover: "Sons of the prophet." Excerpt: "Five soldiers of fortune meet in an Arabian seaport - and the domain of a sheikh begins to tremble." Cover design by Paul Stahr.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 258, no. 6., 1935 September 28; 144 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Creator: Surdez, George
      From cover: "Clarions of youth." Excerpt: "The dying Berber was going to take one more man with him."
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 279, no. 1., 1938 January 22; 144 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 10)
      From cover: "The highland man."
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 290, no. 1., 1939 April 29; 128 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 12, Folder 11)
      From cover: "The wonderful lamp of Thibaut Corday." Excerpt: "There in the Arab night glowed a light brighter than the sun - and there the Legionnaire met a genie to keep a green-eyed siren's promise." Cover painting by Rudolph Belarski.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 298, no. 5., 1940 April 27; 112 pages, 24 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 1)
      From cover: "The golden sword of Samarkand." Excerpt: "He was Tamerlane, the earth shaker, and he held a wild continent in his hand." Cover painting by Marshall Frantz.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 296, no. 3., 1940 January 20; 128 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Creator: Appleton, C. D.
      From cover: "Fate wove a rug." Excerpt: "Every thread was dyed in scarlet drops of blood, and its golden pattern hid the secret of wealth untold." Cover painting by Rudolph Belarski.
    - Argosy New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 296, no. 3., 1940 January 20; 128 pages, 26 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Creator: Goodwin, E. C.
    - Famous fantastic mysteries New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company., 1945 December; 130 pages, 23 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Creator: Haggard, H. Rider
      From cover: "The ancient allan."
    - Famous fantastic mysteries New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company., 1951 January; 112 pages, 22 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Creator: Rohmer, Sax
      From cover: "Brood of the witch-queen." Excerpt: "I cannot doubt that I spent at least one incarnation on the Nile."
    - Fantasic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 12, no. 10., 1950 October; 130 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Creator: Hubbard, L. Ron
      From cover: "The masters of sleep."
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 4, no. 1., 1942 January; 146 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 6)
      From cover: "The daughter of Genghis Khan." Excerpt: "The lovely girl who claimed to be Genghis Khan's daughter could conjure dragons from a fire urn." Cover painting by H.W. McCauley.
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 5, no. 6., 1943 June; 210 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 7)
      From cover: "Genie of Baghdad." Excerpt: "History was changed when a modern girl landed in the middle of ancient Baghdad and told stories." Cover painting by H.W. McCauley.
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 5, no. 6., 1943 June; 210 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 8, no. 5., 1946 November; 176 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 9)
      From cover: "Shadow of the Sphinx." Excerpt: "The sphinx stands patiently in the sands of Egypt - waiting - for someone..." Cover painting by J. Allen St. John.
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 8, no. 5., 1946 November; 176 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 11, no. 2., 1949 February; 154 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 1)
      From cover: "The magician of misty cave." Excerpt: "The terrible forces of creation pulsed through the cave - controlled by a madman's mind!" Cover painting by Arnold Kohn.
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 11, no. 5., 1949 May; 154 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 2)
      From cover: "Lamp of no light." Excerpt: "The lamp was nothing but a piece of bronze - but it held a power Heath had never dreamed of..."
    - Fantastic adventures Chicago, IL: Ziff-Davis Publishing, Vol. 4, no. 1., 1951 February; 130 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 3)
      From cover: "The sword of Ra." Excerpt: "A soldier uses a sword against men in combat–but what weapon can he use against a goddess?" Cover painting by Arnold Kohn.
    - Fantastic novels magazine New York, NY: Frank A. Munsey Company, Vol. 3, no. 5., 1950 January; 130 pages, 19 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Creator: England, George Allan
      From cover: "The flying legion." Excerpt: "Thirty reckless, war-tried flyers - a Master stern and grim of purpose - and all the world their helpless toy as they streaked across the heavens to tear the veil from Earth's last mysteries." Cover painting by Lawrence.
    - Fantastic stories of imagination New York, NY: Ziff-Davis, Vol. 12, no. 8., 1963 August; 130 pages, 19 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 5)
      From cover: "Bazaar of the bizarre." Excerpt: "To Fafhrd, wearing the Cloak of Invisibility and the Blindfold of True Seeing, the scene was the hell-nadir of the universe, where dark devils scuttled and the damned writhed in the grip of black serpents. Thus did they defend Lankhmar against the invasion of the...Bazaar of the Bizarre!"
    - Fate St. Paul, MN: Llewellyn Publications, Vol. 4, no. 7., 1951 October; 130 pages, 19 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 6)
      From cover: "Riddle of the Sphinx." Excerpt: "The Greeks said that the spirit of the courtesan Rhodopis, who married a Pharaoh and was buried in the 3rd pyramid, lives in the Sphinx and appears naked to travelers."
    - Jungle stories New York, NY: Glen-Kel Publishing Company, Vol. 2, no. 7., 1943 May-July; 128 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 7)
      From cover: "Caravan of terror." Excerpt: "Through the weird vastness of the juju forest prowled the walking dead who murdered in the night."
    - Jungle stories New York, NY: Glen-Kel Publishing Company, Vol. 3, no. 7., 1946 May-July; 128 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Creator: Drummond, John Peter
      From cover: "Death seeks for congo treasure." Excerpt: "The death cries of the 'Mad Ones' were filling the jungles with savage terror..."
    - Jungle stories New York, NY: Glen-Kel Publishing Company, Vol. 5, no. 7., 1952 November-January; 128 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 9)
      From cover: "Caravan of terror." Excerpt: "Through the weird vastness of the juju forest prowled the walking dead who murdered in the night." Reprint of 1943 May-July (Summer) issue.
    - Magic carpet magazine Indianapolis, IN: Popular Fiction Publishing Company, Vol. 3, no. 4., 1933 October; 512 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Cover design by M. Brundage.
    - Oriental stories Indianapolis, IN: Popular Fiction Publishing Company, Vol. 1, no. 5., 1931 Summer; 720 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Creator: Kline, Otis Adelbert
      From cover: "The dragoman's slave girl." Excerpt: "A fascinating story of Hameed the Attar, which has all the glamour of the "Arabian Nights."
    - Short stories New York, NY: Doubleday, Doran and Company, Vol. 132, no. 4., 1930 August 25; 176 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 14, Folder 12)
      From cover: "Treasure of the Pharoahs."
    - Spicy-adventure stories Wilmington, DE: Culture Publications, Vol. 2, no. 2., 1935 May; 128 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 1)
      From cover: "Desert madness." Pulp Replica Edition by Girasol Collectables, Incorporated.
    - Spicy-adventure stories Wilmington, DE: Culture Publications, Vol. 7, no. 2., 1937 November; 128 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 2)
      From cover: "Hell in Darien."
    - Spider Chicago, IL: Popular Publications, Vol. 10, no. 2., 1936 November; 112 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Creator: Stockbridge, Grant
      From cover: "City of dreadful night." Excerpt: "The city of New York was held in thrall by that sinister menace from the East, the ageless man out of Egypt, Tang-akhmut, the mass murderer." Cover painting by John Howitt.
    - Spider Chicago, IL: Popular Publications, Vol. 10, no. 1., 1936 October; 112 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 4)
      From cover: "The devil's death-dwarfs." Excerpt: "Only Tang-akhmut, the sinister Egyptian, the man whose vices were ageless and uncounted, could be engineering those wholesale murders, torturings, and mass kidnappings. Cover painting by John Howitt.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1927 December; 864 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Creator: Price, E. Hoffman
      From cover: "The infidel's daughter." Excerpt: "Landan built a ziggurat in Feringhistan that he might aspire to the Hundred and One Strange Kisses of Sarpanit." Cover painting by Hugh Rankin.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company, Vol. 8, no. 6., 1929 June; 864 pages, 24 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Creator: Quinn, Seabury
      From cover: "The house of golden masks." Cover painting by Hugh Rankin.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1930 April; 576 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 7)
      From cover: "The dust of Egypt."
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company, Vol. 15, no.2., 1930 February; 288 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 8)
      From cover: "Thirsty blades." Excerpt: "A swift moving tale of the devil- worshipers of Kurdistan, and the colossal issues that hung upon the clash of blades." Cover painting by Hugh Rankin.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company, Vol. 15, no.2., 1930 February; 288 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1935 February; 79 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 9)
      From cover: "The web of living death." Cover painting by M. Brundage.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1938 November; 640 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 10)
      From cover: "I found Cleopatra."
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1942 January; 128 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 11)
      From cover: "Who can escape?" Excerpt: "Death seems so certain, so final - but the land of the unquiet dead has many exits."
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1945 May; 79 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 12)
      From cover: "Lords of the ghostlands." Excerpt: "To be jerked out of the quiet restfulness of your grave and shipped across four thousand miles of water...but then any mummy might be called unlucky!" Cover painting by A.R. Tilburne.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1945 May; 79 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1933 May; 79 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Creator: Williamson, Jack
      From cover: "Golden blood." Excerpt: "A powerful novel of weird adventures in the hidden land of Arabia." Cover painting by J. Allen St. John.
    - Weird tales Philadelphia, PA: Terminus Publishing Company., 1946 January; 79 pages, 25 centimeters (Box 16, Folder 2)
      From cover: "Kurban." Excerpt: "Like Pharaoh's necromancers, he cast his rod upon the earth and it became a live, hissing serpent." Cover painting by A.R. Tilburne.